Hi everybody! I'm glad to see you on the channel again! :)
Do you like this wonderful blue color?
I'm thrilled with him.  ♡＼(￣▽￣)／♡
This jelly is like the sky. :)
I made it apple-flavored.
This marshmallow is like a cloud.
Do you like this jelly spoon? :)
So delicious!
Blue meringue. It reminds me of a flower. (✿◠‿◠)
Eyeball gummy. (*˘︶˘*)
Very tasty. :)
Melts in mouth!
I think it will be even tastier. :)
Inside is a very delicious strawberry jam.
The candy is a little sour. :)
Blue macaroon with vanilla cream. :)
Very tasty and tender. :)
I like this combination.
(✯◡✯)
Very nice blue lollipop.
So sweet. :)
Very tasty! ♡＼(￣▽￣)／♡
Marshmallow Plane. :) Do you like it?
It tastes like vanilla. :)
I like its airy structure so much. :)
So gentle!
See you soon!
Please like, subscribe to the channel and hit the bell icon!